<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<catalog>
  <genre type="Comedy">
    <collection>
    <picture>free guy.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>Free Guy</dvd>
      <price>9.99</price>
      <description>It is the story of a bank teller who discovers he is actually a background player in an open-world video game, decides to become the hero of his own story.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection>
    <picture>scary movie 2.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>Scary Movie 2</dvd>
      <price>7.00</price>
      <description>Four teens are tricked by Professor Oldman into visiting a haunted house for a school project.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection tv-series="true">
    <picture>friends.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>Friends</dvd>
      <price>75.00</price>
       <description>Friends is a 90's Comedy TV show, based in Manhattan, about 6 friends who go through just about every life experience imaginable together; love, marriage, divorce, children, heartbreaks, fights, new jobs and job losses and all sorts of drama.</description>
    </collection>
  </genre>
  <genre type="Drama">
    <collection>
    <picture>sweet november.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>Sweet November</dvd>
      <price>9.99</price>
       <description>A workaholic executive, and an unconventional woman agree to a personal relationship for a short period. In this short period she changes his life. The story centers around a man and a woman, whose fates are intertwined and will change forever.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection>
    <picture>forrest gump.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>Forrest Gump</dvd>
      <price>11.99</price>
      <description>Forrest Gump is a simple man with a low I.Q. but good intentions. He is running through childhood with his best and only friend Jenny. His 'mama' teaches him the ways of life and leaves him to choose his destiny.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection tv-series="true">
    <picture>gilmore girls.jpeg</picture>
      <dvd>Gilmore Girls</dvd>
      <price>89.99</price>
      <description>Gilmore Girls is an American TV series, starring Lorelai and Rory as a mother and a daughter who are more friends than mother and daughter and who both dream of pursuing satisfaction in their love relationships and their careers</description>
    </collection>
  </genre>
  <genre type="Romance">
    <collection>
    <picture>somewhere in time.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>Somewhere in Time</dvd>
      <price>12.99</price>
      <description>A Chicago playwright uses self-hypnosis to travel back in time and meet the actress whose vintage portrait hangs in a grand hotel.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection>
    <picture>titanic.png</picture>
      <dvd>Titanic</dvd>
      <price>12.99</price>
      <description>Titanic is a 1997 American epic romantic disaster movie. The movie is about the 1912 sinking of the RMS Titanic.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection tv-series="true">
    <picture>outlander.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>Outlander</dvd>
      <price>125.00</price>
      <description>Outlander follows the story of Claire Randall, a married combat nurse from 1945 who is mysteriously swept back in time to 1743, where she is immediately thrown into an unknown world where her life is threatened.</description>
    </collection>
  </genre>
  <genre type="Horror">
    <collection>
    <picture>the exorcist.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>The Exorcist</dvd>
      <price>7.50</price>
      <description>It follows the demonic possession of a 12 year-old girl and her mother's attempt to rescue her through an exorcism conducted by two Catholic priests.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection>
    <picture>the sixth sense.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>The Sixth Sense</dvd>
      <price>9.99</price>
      <description>The film tells the story of Kole Sear, a troubled, isolated boy who is able to see and talk to the dead, and an equally troubled child psychologist named Malcolm Crowe who tries to help him.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection tv-series="true">
    <picture>AHS.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>American Horror Stories</dvd>
      <price>100.00</price>
      <description>Each season is conceived as a self-contained miniseries, following a different set of characters and settings, and a storyline with its own "beginning, middle, and end." Some plot elements of each season are loosely inspired by true events.</description>
    </collection>
  </genre>
  <genre type="Action">
    <collection>
    <picture>gladiator.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>Gladiator</dvd>
      <price>9.99</price>
      <description>A former Roman General sets out to exact vengeance against the corrupt emperor who murdered his family and sent him into slavery.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection>
    <picture>the last duel.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>The Last Duel</dvd>
      <price>16.99</price>
      <description>Based on the true story of France's last trial by combat in the Middle Ages. Knight Jean de Carrouges challenges his former friend Jacques Le Gris to a duel after Jean's wife Marguerite accuses Le Gris of rape. Told in multiple "Rashomon-style" points of view.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection tv-series="true">
    <picture>buffy.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>Buffy The Vampire Slayer</dvd>
      <price>79.99</price>
      <description>A young woman, destined to slay vampires, demons and other infernal creatures, deals with her life fighting evil, with the help of her friends. </description>
    </collection>
  </genre>
  <genre type="Sci-fi">
    <collection>
    <picture>matrix.png</picture>
      <dvd> The Matrix</dvd>
      <price>19.99</price>
      <description>The film describes a future in which reality perceived by humans is actually the Matrix, a simulated reality created by sentient Machines in order to pacify and subdue the human population while their bodies' heat and electrical activity are used as an energy source.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection>
    <picture>the butterfly effect.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>The Butterfly Effect</dvd>
      <price>16.99</price>
      <description>The film draws heavily on flashbacks of the characters' lives at ages 7 and 13 and presents several alternative present-day outcomes as Evan attempts to change the past, before settling on a final outcome.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection tv-series="true">
    <picture>the mandalorian.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>The Mandalorian</dvd>
      <price>25.00</price>
      <description>After the stories of Jango and Boba Fett, another warrior emerges in the Star Wars universe. “The Mandalorian” is set after the fall of the Empire and before the emergence of the First Order. We follow the travails of a lone gunfighter in the outer reaches of the galaxy, far from the authority of the New Republic.</description>
    </collection>
  </genre>
<genre type="Classic">
    <collection>
    <picture>breakfast.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>Breakfast at Tiffany's</dvd>
      <price>19.99</price>
      <description>It is the story of a young woman in World War II-era New York who hobnobs with famous people, gets into a lot of trouble, and breaks many hearts along the way, all while struggling to find her place in the world.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection>
    <picture>gone with the wind.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>Gone with the wind</dvd>
      <price>15.20</price>
      <description>Set in the American South against the backdrop of the American Civil War and the Reconstruction era, the film tells the story of Scarlett O'Hara, the strong-willed daughter of a Georgia plantation owner.</description>
    </collection>
    <collection tv-series="true">
    <picture>simpsons.jpg</picture>
      <dvd>The Simpsons</dvd>
      <price>250.00</price>
      <description>The series is a satirical depiction of American life, epitomized by the Simpson family, which consists of Homer, Marge, Bart, Lisa, and Maggie. The show is set in the fictional town of Springfield and parodies American culture and society, television, and the human condition.</description>
    </collection>
  </genre>
</catalog>